Nahid Jahani Web Developer

Personal Info

Addressee:

Halifax St. Burnaby

Phone Number:

6044419287

Email:

Jahaninahide@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

http://linkedin.com/in/nahidjahani- 709134145

Soft Skills

Great at Problem solving

Collaborations

Time management

Good Leadership

Technical Skills

JavaScript

Html

C#

React.js

WordPress

Languages

English

Farsi

Turkish

Career Objective

Joiner web Developer with more than 3 years of experience in designing and developing web design, testing, and training staff technologies. Well-versed in numerous programing languages including JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS, CorelDraw, Adobe and Photoshop. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Proficient Skills

- Comprehensive web designer using a platform based on successful project completion and reviews, for artists and businesses.
- Strong organization and communications skills.
- Curate effective content to communicate brand messages in fresh, reactive ways.
- Self-motivated with outstanding time management.
- Understanding of labor regulations and legal codes.
- Attentive listening and effective oral communication skills.

Experience

2021- present Web Designer Faith Fire Surrey, BC

- Developed project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.
- Contacted clients to obtain more information and discusses design options.
- Employed mastery of designer languages CorelDraw, Adobe Photoshop.

2014-2017 Web Developer Shirin Asal, Co Tabriz, Iran

Education

2009-2013 Bachler of Software Engineer

Jahad Daneshgahi Tabriz, Iran

Certificates

2019-2021 BCIT C#, Html, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

2020- 2201 UDEMY React.js, Hooks, Redux, WordPress